🚣 Download

Print

**E**mail

A Spell Check

**RESUME SECTIONS** 

■ Professional Summary

Heading

Links

½ Skills

**Work History** 

Accomplishments

♣ Add a section

**Education** 

More Options

# Amal Saed Hassan Mohammed

Faisel, Giza (+20)10-239-712-33 amlsaed02@gmail.com

https://github.com/Aml02| https://codepen.io/aml-saed/| https://www.linkedin.com/in/aml-saed-

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A Front-end Developer that work independently or in a team, creative and innovative, And have excellent communication skills, Easily implement new ideas, Self-motivated, Able to work under pressure, Writing well organized and clean code, I hope working in a creative company where I can invest my qualifications and learn more & increase my experience.

### **SKILLS**

- Html5
- css3
- javascript
- ES6
- typescript
- Jquery
- Angular photoshop
- php
- mysql
- git

- github
- gulb
- Information Technology
- Web technology
- · Code debugging
- websites
- Ul improvements
- Project documentation
- · Website optimization

**WORK HISTORY** 

FRONT END DEVELOPER | 09/2018 to 10/2018

الجيزة - Bit&Bits

- OJT
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.

FRONT END DEVELOPER | 08/2018 to 09/2018

NTI - Smart Village, Giza Governorate

- Final project
- Designed and developed layouts to meet usability and performance requirements for

**FRONT END DEVELOPER** | 04/2018 to 08/2018

Vadecom - فيصل, Giza Governorate

• Trained junior members of web team , converting PSD into a full responsive websites .

## **EDUCATION**

National Telecommunication Institute (NTI) | A 6-Month scholarship, full stack track, Web technology (design& development)

Ministry of Communications and Information Technology Smart Village Branch.

Enrolled in One Million Arab coders(front end track)

faculty of Science. University: Zagazig University | B.Sc 2017

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- 2 months training as front end developer at Vadecom Company for web solutions.
- 1 month training as front end developer at Bit&Bits Company for web design Technical Skills:.
- JAVA SCRIPT.
- J QUERY.
- BOOTSTRAP 4.
- Css3.
- HTML5.
- ES6.
- PHP
- · MYSQL. PHOTOSHOP.
- Git/Github Soft Skills:.
- Flexible and Good communication skills.
- Interactive and fast enough to learn new technologies.
- Team player, self-learner.
- Ability to think "outside the box".
- Shares information and accepts feedback easily.
- Notes: You can see a sample of my code on github: https://github.com/Aml02 2 | Page.

TERMS & CONDITIONS | PRIVACY POLICY | CONTACT US

**TEMPLATE** Managerial ▼ **FORMATTING** 

**SAVE & NEXT**